<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>xfel</title>
    <link>https://fernando-jascovich.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on xfel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fernando-jascovich.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a MiniDox</title>
      <link>https://fernando-jascovich.github.io/posts/building-a-minidox/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fernando-jascovich.github.io/posts/building-a-minidox/</guid>
      <description>I built my first mechanical keyboard, a MiniDox.
  Motivation  It was easy? nope. I already had experience doing something similar? nope. I had even held a solder for one second before? nope. I knew somthing about keyboards before (besides using one, of course)? nope.  So&amp;hellip; why? Well, to be completely honest, for fun mainly. I got my first comments about something called &amp;ldquo;mechanical keyboard&amp;rdquo; thanks to geekymartian, he built an ErgoDox and then others (two MiniDoxs and counting).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>android-env.el -&gt; My first Melpa pkg</title>
      <link>https://fernando-jascovich.github.io/posts/android-env/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fernando-jascovich.github.io/posts/android-env/</guid>
      <description>I got published my first package to Melpa.
android-env is a helper for those eager to do Android using Emacs. I know, is not the mainstream way to do it, but Emacs is my home.
  Is a tiny little thing but it really helps me on my daily work. Thanks to Chris Rayner and Steve Purcell for being so helpful and guiding me into know a little about elisp standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>xfel-init-project.el</title>
      <link>https://fernando-jascovich.github.io/posts/xfel-init-project.el/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fernando-jascovich.github.io/posts/xfel-init-project.el/</guid>
      <description>After trying some project management tools for emacs, I found several great and thorough packages which I used on a daily basis for software development:
 Projectile Ivy  But then, after a while of using those great tools, I noticed that there are little functionality that I really use from those packages. And, as an excuse for exercising elisp, I decided to write some&amp;hellip; let&amp;rsquo;s say &amp;ldquo;helpers&amp;rdquo; for working every day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>